<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Bipolar Artist</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Bipolar Artist</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>es-es</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 14 Oct 2020 18:48:21 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Bipolar Artist - Creating Change</title>
      <link>/creating-change.html</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Oct 2020 18:48:21 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/creating-change.html</guid>
      <description>Creating Change Creating change is something that’s always at the forefront of our minds, whether it be helping a client rebrand from scratch or encouraging team members to stretch themselves with a new language.
Client time A fresh image Giving a brand a funky fresh new image is always exciting. And we’re often the lucky ones who get to help, one such rebranding example is Proactiv, the skin care market leader in the US.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bipolar Artist - Creating Emotions</title>
      <link>/creating-emotions.html</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Oct 2020 18:48:21 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/creating-emotions.html</guid>
      <description>Creating Emotions Every time we start a project we ask ourselves, how do we want people to feel? Making something look pretty is one thing, but we want to rock your world.
Client time	A Joyous Republic A disruptive UK mobile network was looking for a way to take employee engagement to the next level. We donned our thinking caps and after some careful planning and teamwork, the Joyous Republic of giffgaff was born.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bipolar Artist - Embracing Change</title>
      <link>/embracing-change.html</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Oct 2020 18:48:21 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/embracing-change.html</guid>
      <description>Embracing Change The early days were all about print projects like brochures, flyers and posters. Then the world changed and now our days whizz by working on websites, digital designs and other online adventures.
Client time	Excitement control We don’t make changes for the sake of it so we carried out a complete SEO audit of the Sky Spain site before proposing any amendments. Our recommendations helped give their rankings a bump.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bipolar Artist - Embracing Emotions</title>
      <link>/embracing-emotions.html</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Oct 2020 18:48:21 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/embracing-emotions.html</guid>
      <description>Embracing Emotions It all started in our childhood. Our families shared their passions with us and they stuck. They lit a wick and ignited a creative flame.
ME Taking it to the rooftop A top collection of luxury hotels wanted to boost its rooftop bar. Fires ignited in our belly. We couldn&#39;t resist joining forces with ME by Melia. And we&#39;re heading straight for the top.
A team of greats who do not know the meaning of the word impossible.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bipolar Artist - Inspiring Change</title>
      <link>/inspiring-change.html</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Oct 2020 18:48:21 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/inspiring-change.html</guid>
      <description>Inspiring Change Change can start with an idea, a sketch, a conversation or a brainstorm in a coffee shop. We don’t know how it happens we’re just experts at making sure it does.
Client time Social glitter Reaching a very large audience is never easy, but we&#39;re experts at taking brands to the next level. Take a look at how we smashed Virgin UAE&#39;s social channels with punchy on-brand campaigns.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bipolar Artist - Inspiring Emotions</title>
      <link>/inspiring-emotions.html</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Oct 2020 18:48:21 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/inspiring-emotions.html</guid>
      <description>Inspiring Emotions We pour everything into our designs and want to inspire a range of emotions in people so they don’t just go “oh” but “aw” as well. Motion Animating folks with animation We love a challenge. Like getting customers excited about a client’s new financial service in a fun and friendly way. Take a look at the result.
You guys rock. The gameplan video was a total joy, super clear and has a lovely warmth to it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>/contact.html</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Oct 2020 18:48:21 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/contact.html</guid>
      <description> If you want to listen to our beautiful and inspiring voices:
(+34) 916 229 568
Contact Us &amp;nbsp;Send Message Information was sent. Thanks for your message
This is where we&#39;re based </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
